Inventory of the Fu-mei Chang Chen (張陳富美) collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Fu-mei Chang Chen (張陳富美) collection
1984-1994
93101
Hoover Institution Archives
4 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (2.4 linear feet)
Election campaign literature, and bulletins, relating to elections, political conditions, and civil rights in Taiwan.
Chen, Fu-mei Chang, collector.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1993.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Election campaign literature, and bulletins, relating to elections, political conditions, and civil rights in Taiwan.
Civil rights--Taiwan.; Elections--Taiwan.; Taiwan--Politics and government.
- Clean election campaign movement 净化选举运动, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:17)
- A monthly publication for private circulation dealing with current affairs in Taiwan -- Yuan 缘 -- 仅供内部传阅，讨论台湾时事的月发行刊物, Dec., 1984 - Sep., 1987 (Box-folder 2:1-7)
- Miscellaneous propaganda from major parties in Taiwan 国民党文宣，民进党文宣及其他, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:12)
- Taiwan -- Legislative committee election 台湾 -- 立法委员会选举, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 3: 5-7)
- Taiwan -- Legislative Yuan candidates from vocational group 台湾 -- 立法委员会职业团体候选人, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:2)
- Taiwan -- Assembly election 台湾 -- 议会选举, Dec. 21, 1991 (Box-folder 2: 10)
- Democratic Progressive Party's 7th Anniversary Celebration; Democratic Progressive Party 民进党建党7周年庆典 民主进步党“核四公投10万签名活动“, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 4:3)
- Democratic Progressive Party notice, letters and other materials 民主进步党信函，党章党纲和宣传资料, 1994 (Box-folder 4:4)
- Democratic Progressive Party Congress materials 民进党第六届第一次全国代表大会会议资料, 1994 (Box-folder 4:5)
- Democratic Progressive Party Congress materials 民进党全国代表大会资料, 1992 (Box-folder 4:6)
- Democratic Progressive Party meeting agenda 民进党第五届中央党部会议议程, 1993 (Box-folder 4:7)
- Newspaper clippings 剪报, 1994 (Box-folder 4:12)
- Newspaper clippings and campaign posters 其他资料 -- 剪报及竞选宣传资料, 1993 - 1994 (Box 5)
- Gaoxiong county -- Provincial assemblymen 高雄县 -- 省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:8)
- Gaoxiong county -- Legislative committee members 高雄县 -- 立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:14)
- Gaoxiong county -- County head 高雄县 -- 县长, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:11)
- Gaoxiong city -- Legislative committee member 高雄市 -- 立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:7)
- Gaoxiong city -- City councilmen 高雄市 -- 市议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:9)
- Hualian county -- County head 花莲县 -- 县长, 1993 (Box-folder 4:8)
- Linyun county -- Legislative committee members 霖云县 -- 立法委员, undated (Box-folder 4:9)
- Miaoli county -- Provincial assemblymen 苗栗县 -- 省议员, undated (Box-folder 1:5)
- Nantou county -- District magistrate, legislates and provincial assemblymen 南投县 -- 县长, 全国立法委员和省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 2: 9)
- Pindong county -- County head 屏东县 -- 县长, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:6)
- Tainan city -- Mayor and legislative committee member 台南市-- 市长，立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:4)
- Taipei county -- Provincial assemblymen 台北县 -- 省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:19)
- Taipei county -- Legislative committee members 台北县 -- 立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:21)
- Taipei county -- County head 台北县 -- 县长, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:10)
- Taipei city -- Legislative committee members 台北市 -- 立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:20)
- Taipei city -- Council member 台北市-- 市议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:1)
- Taizhong county -- Legislative committee members 台中县 -- 立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:12)
- Taizhong county -- Provincial assemblymen and legislators 台中县 -- 省议员和立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 2: 8)
- Taizhong county -- Provincial assemblymen 台中县 -- 省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:16)
- Taizhong county -- County head 台中县 -- 县长, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:15)
- Taizhong county -- County head 台中县 -- 县长, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 3: 3)
- Taizhong city -- Legislative committee members 台中市 -- 立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 4：10)
- Taizhong city -- Legislative committee members 台中市 -- 立法委员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 2: 11)
- Taizhong city -- Provincial assemblymen 台中市 -- 省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 4：11)
- Taizhong city -- Mayor 台中市 -- 市长, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:22)
- Taizhong city -- Mayor and provincial assemblymen 台中市 -- 市长和省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 3: 2)
- Taizhong city election 台中市选举, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 3: 4)
- Taizhong city -- Mayor and assemblymen 台中市 -- 市长和议员, 1993 - 1994 (Box-folder 4:1)
- Taoyuan county -- County head 桃园县 -- 县长, undated (Box-folder 1:3)
- Xinzhu city -- Mayor, legislates and provincial assemblymen 新竹市 -- 市长，立法委员和省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 1:18)
- Zhanghua county -- County head, national legislates and provincial assemblymen 彰化县 -- 县长，立法委员和省议员, Dec., 1989 (Box-folder 3: 1)
- Zhuanghua county - County head 彰化县 -- 县长, 1993 (Box-folder 4:2)